A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Awards in Arts Education Program, RG 7 FA776
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Applications
  - Applications Dated 1983 for Year 3 (1984)
    - Connecticut, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 960-966)
      Including: Darien High, William H. Hall High, Hamden High, Illing Junior High, Newtown High, Squadron Line School, Windsor High.
    - Delaware, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 967-968)
      Including: Marbrook Elementary, Newark High.
    - District of Columbia, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 969)
      Including: Duke Ellington School of the Arts.
    - Florida, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 970-979)
      Including: Boyd H. Anderson High, Banyan Elementary, Booker Visual and Performing Arts Center, Cove Elementary, Cushman School, Gemini Elementary, Hungerford Elementary, Lake Mary High, Sabal Point Elementary, Southwood Junior High.
    - Georgia, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 980-985)
      Including: Armuchee High, Bibb City Elementary, College Street Elementary, Davidson Fine Arts School, Fulton County School System, Walker Park School.
    - Hawaii, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 986-987)
      Including: Kohala High and Elementary, Waianae High.
    - Idaho, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 988)
      Including: Boise Elementary Schools - Arts in Education Consortium.
    - Illinois, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 989-992)
      Including: Auburn High, Champaign Middle School at Columbia, Lyons, Booker T. Washington Elementary.
    - Indiana, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 993-994)
      Including: Flaget Elementary, West Lafayette Junior High.
    - Kentucky, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 995-996)
      Including: Hardin County Educational Television, Norton and Chenoweth Elementary Schools.
    - Louisiana, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 997-997A)
      Including: Edward Hynes Elementary, New Orleans Center for Creative Arts.
    - Maine, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 998)
      Including: Thornton Academy.
    - Maryland, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 999-1002)
      Including: Chevy Chase Elementary, North Frederick Elementary, Eleanor Roosevelt High, Valley Elementary.
    - Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 1003-1009)
      Including: Baker School, Boxford Schools, Cambridge Rindge and Latin School, Kennedy Elementary, Pearl Street School, Charles H. Taylor School, Wellesley High.
    - Michigan, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 1010-1015)
      Including: Edmonson Elementary, Grosse Pointe North High, Hemlock Middle, Martin Luther King, Jr. Senior High, Paw Paw High, Southeastern Junior High.
    - Minnesota, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 1016, Box 57, Folder 1017-1022)
      Including: Apple Valley High, Central Performing Arts, Fulton Elementary, Jordan Elementary, Northern Elementary, West Concord Elementary, Wyola Elementary.
    - Mississippi, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1023)
      Including: Brandon High.
    - Montana, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1024)
      Including: Powell County High.
    - Nebraska, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1025)
      Including: Meadows Elementary.
    - Nevada, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1026)
      Including: Fay Herron Year-Round School.
    - New Hampshire, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1027)
      Including: Manchester High School Central.
    - New Jersey, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1028-1037)
      Including: Arts High, Byram Township Intermediate, East Brunswick High, Erial Elementary, Florence M. Gaudineer Middle, Matawan Regional High, Oceanville School, Arthur Rann Middle, Roosevelt Elementary, Vernon Township High.
    - New Mexico, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1038-1043)
      Including: Española Valley High, Hoover Middle, Mountain Elementary, New Mexico School for the Visually Handicapped, Pojoaque Valley High, Tibbets Junior High.
    - New York, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1044-1060, Box 58, Folder 1061-1080)
      Including: William Alexander Junior High 51-Brooklyn, Ardsley Middle, Louis Armstrong Middle/Intermediate 227Q-Queens, Buffalo Academy for Visual and Performing Arts, Alexander Burger Intermediate 139-Bronx, The Center School, Cicero High, Roberto Clemente School of the Arts, Corlears Junior High 56, Denton Avenue School, Erasmus Hall High, John Ericsson Junior High, Fairport High, Harbor Junior High for the Performing Arts, Hastings High, Rafael Hernández Intermediate 116-Bronx, Herricks High, John Jay High, John F. Kennedy High, Meyer Levin Junior High 285-Brooklyn, Lindenhurst High, The Manhattan East School, Mineola High, Nottingham High, Penfield High, Port Richmond High, Public School 85X-Bronx, Public School 138-Bronx [EMPTY FOLDER], Public School 166-Queens-The Henry Gradstein School, Public School 189/Bilingual School, Public School 242K-Brooklyn, Public School 251 Early Childhood School-Queens, Richmond Hill High, Satellite Academy, Union-Endicott Senior High, Valley Stream Central High, Daniel Webster School.
    - North Carolina, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1081-1085)
      Including: Career Center-Winston Salem/Forsyth County Schools, Chapel Hill High, Philo Junior High, Pitt County Schools, Rockingham Junior High.
    - Ohio, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1086-1091)
      Including: Duxberry Park Alternative School-Arts Impact, Fort Hayes Career Center, Miller High Southern Local, Rosemore Junior High and Beechwood Elementary, Tower Heights Middle, Warren High and Barlow-Vincent Elementary.
    - Oklahoma, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1092-1094)
      Including: Emerson Elementary, Garfield Elementary, Booker T. Washington High.
    - Oregon, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1095-1098)
      Including: Carus School District #29, Jefferson High, Richmond Elementary.
    - Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1099-1103, Box 59, Folder 1104-1108)
      Including: East Stroudsburg Junior/Senior High Schools, Stephen Girard School, Greater Johnstown High, Harrisburg Arts Magnet School, John Story Jenks School, Rogers School for Creative and Performing Arts, Scenic Hills Elementary, Selinsgrove Area Middle, William A. Shoemaker School, Tawanka Elementary.
    - Rhode Island, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1109)
      Including: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. School.
    - South Carolina, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1110-1117)
      Including: Greer Middle, Wade Hampton High, Laurens District 55 Schools, Olanta Elementary, Pacolet Elementary, Pelham Road Elementary, Spring Valley High.
    - South Dakota, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1118)
      Including: Stevens High.
    - Tennessee, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1119)
      Including: Big Ridge Elementary.
    - Texas, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1120-1125)
      Including: Bowie High, Blanche K. Bruce Elementary Music Academy, Ford Elementary, J. Houston Elementary, The People's Workshop for the Visual and Performing Arts, Sims Elementary.
    - Utah, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1126)
      Including: Davis High.
    - Vermont, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1127)
      Including: Lyndon Institute, Inc.
    - Virgin Islands, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1128)
    - Virginia, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1129-1140)
      Including: Drew Model School, Falls Church Elementary Schools, Glencarlyn Elementary, Granby High, Lee-Davis High, Nottingham Elementary, Old Donation Center for the Gifted and Talented, Patrick Henry High, South Lakes High, Taylor Elementary, Washington-Lee High, Woodville Elementary.
    - Washington, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1141-1146)
      Including: Amboy Intermediate, Discovery Elementary, McMurray Intermediate, Olalla Elementary, Pullman School District, Summit K-12 Alternative School.
    - West Virginia, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1147-1148)
      Including: Cameron Elementary, Short Gap Primary.
    - Wisconsin, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1149-1151)
      Including: Birchwood Public Schools, Elm Creative Arts School, Wausau West High.
  - Applications Dated 1984 for Year 4 (1985)
    - Alabama, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1152-1156)
      Including: George Washington Carver High, Foley Schools, Ophelia S. Hill Elementary, McElwain Elementary/Putnam Middle Schools, Palmer Pillans Middle.
    - Alaska, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1157-1158)
      Including: East Anchorage High, Wasilla High.
    - Arizona, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1159-1168)
      Including: Carrillo Intermediate, Doolen Junior High, Elbert A. Gump Junior High for Adaptive Education, Ganado High, Horizon High, Mesa Junior High, Miller Valley School, Santa Rita High, Shadow Mountain High, Shea Middle.
    - Arkansas, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1169)
      Including: Highland High.
    - California, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1170-1207)
      Including: Bancroft Junior High Performing Arts Magnet School, Bellflower High, Buena Vista Elementary, Henry Clay Junior High, Crescent Elementary, Dana Junior High, Dixie Canyon Avenue School, Dunbar Elementary, Farmdale Elementary, Benjamin Franklin Middle, Gardenhill School, Gonsalves Elementary, Ideal Foundation, Jefferson Elementary, Lorena Street School, Los Alisos Intermediate, Loyola Village Fine and Performing Arts Magnet Center, Magnolia Elementary, Mission Viejo High, New Traditions School, Newton Junior High, Rancho Canada Elementary, Reseda High, Saticoy Elementary, The School for the Creative and Performing Arts, Soquel High, South Shores Elementary School Visual and Performing Arts Center, Commodore Stockton School, Third Street School, Vintage High, Vista High, Walnut High, George Washington High, West Hollywood Opportunity Center, Westchester High, Helen Wittman Elementary, Woodlake Avenue Elementary, Malcolm X School.
    - Colorado, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 1208-1212)
      Including: Audubon Elementary, Gardner School, Gilpin Extended Day School, Lincoln Elementary and Philips Elementary Schools, Marshdale Elementary.
    - Connecticut, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 1213-1233)
      Including: Avon Middle, Bacon Academy-Central School, Bethlehem Elementary and Mitchell Elementary Schools, Cider Mill School, Clooman Middle, Darien High, Farmington High, Glenville School, Hamden High, Holmes School, Lebanon Elementary, John Lyman School, Manchester High, New Canaan High, Shepaug Valley School, Somers High, South Windsor High, Staples High, Valley Regional High, Woodstock Public School.
    - District of Columbia, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 1234-1237)
      Including: Browne Junior High, Eliot Junior High, Jefferson Junior High, Woodrow Wilson High.
    - Florida, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1238-1251)
      Including: Bagdad Elementary, John S Davidson Fine Arts School, Edgewater Public School, J. J. Finley Elementary, Alexander D. Henderson University School, Jensen Beach Elementary, Key Largo Elementary, Lealman Comprehensive Middle, Mainland Senior High, Oriole Beach Elementary, Pace High, Performing and Visual Arts Center, Southwood Junior High, Spring Hill Middle.
    - Georgia, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1252-1255)
      Including: Briarcliff High, Cedar Shoals High, Pebblebrook High, Union County Schools.
    - Hawaii, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1256-1257)
      Including: Barbers Point Elementary, Kapaa High and Intermediate.
    - Idaho, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1258-1260)
      Including: Elk River Public School, Dora Erickson Elementary, Moscow Junior High.
    - Illinois, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1261-1278)
      Including: Arbor Park District No. 145, Cassell Elementary and Keller Elementary Schools, Chatham Elementary, Dakota Community Unit District No. 201, Richard Edwards Elementary, Elmwood Community Unit School District No. 322, Lake Bluff Junior High, Lake Bluff School District No. 65, Liberty Elementary, E. F. Lindop School, Owen Marsh Elementary, McClery Elementary and Greenman Elementary Schools, Niles North High, Olive School, F. W. Reilly Elementary, Robeson Elementary, Booker T. Washington School, Willowbrook High.
    - Indiana, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1279-1280)
      Including: River Valley Middle, Westlane Middle.
    - Iowa, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1281, 1282, 1283, 1284)
      Including: Lakeview Elementary, George Washington Senior High, Waverly-Shell Rock Community High.
      Folder 1283A - CLOSED
    - Iowa, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 1283A)
    - Kansas, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1285-1286)
      Including: Pearl Kensler Elementary, Soderstrom Elementary and Middle School.
    - Louisiana, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1287-1294, Box 64, Folder 1295-1298)
      Including: McDonogh 15 Elementary, New Orleans Center for Creative Arts, South Highlands Magnet School.
    - Maryland, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1299-1306)
      Including: Abbottston Elementary, Bel Air High, Centennial High, Chesapeake High, Chevy Chase Elementary, Stephen Decatur High, Hamilton Junior High, William Tyler Page Elementary.
    - Massachusetts, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1307-1318)
      Including: Amherst Regional Junior and Senior High, Barnstable Middle, Martha M. Burnell Campus Elementary, Hyman Fine Elementary, Liberty School, Morse Pond School, New North Community School, Newton North High, Northborough Middle, Rockland High, Washington Community Magnet School.
    - Michigan, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1319-1323)
      Including: Central Elementary, Garber High, Northern High, St. Helen Elementary, Von Steuben Middle.
    - Minnesota, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1324-1327)
      Including: Anwatin Junior High, Apple Valley High, Cambridge Elementary, Robbinsdale Armstrong Senior High.
    - Mississippi, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1328-1329)
      Including: Academic and Performing Arts Center, Perry Central High.
    - Missouri, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1330-1336)
      Including: Becky-David Primary School, Henry Elementary, Honors Art/4th R Gallery, Parkway East Junior High, University City Senior High, Wydon Junior High.
    - Montana, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1337)
      Including: Lodge Grass High.
    - Nebraska, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1338-1339)
      Including: Arbor Heights Junior High, Palmyra High.
    - Nevada, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1340)
      Including: Kingsbury Middle.
    - New Hampshire, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1341-1342)
      Including: Jonathan M. Daniels School, E. G. Sherburne School.
    - New Jersey, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1343-1352)
      Including: John Adams Junior High, Arts High, Dunellen High, Glen Ridge High, Hasbrouck Heights High, Holmdel Intermediate, Lacey Township Middle, Meadowbrook School, Passaic Valley Regional High, Rutherford High.
    - New Mexico, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1353)
      Including: Longfellow Community School.
    - New York, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1354-1362, Box 66, Folder 1363-1368)
      Including: Alexander Burger I. S. 139-Bronx, Arlington High, Binghamton High, Blind Brook High, Pablo Casils I. S. 181X-Bronx, Central Park East School, Denton Avenue School, The Henry Gradstein School-P. S. 166-Queens, Meyer Levin Junior High, Manhattan East-Center for Arts and Academics, Nassau BOCES Cultural Arts Center, Public School 52K-Brooklyn, Satellite IV Junior High, School Number Six.
    - North Carolina, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1369-1371)
      Including: Ligon Gifted and Talented Middle, Lincoln Heights and Fuquay-Varina Gifted and Talented Magnet Elementary Schools, Washington Elementary.
    - Ohio, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1372-1381)
      Including: Johnny Appleseed Middle, Cuyahoga Heights Elementary, Etna Road Elementary, Huntington Elementary, Robert E. Lucas Intermediate, Princeton High, The School for Creative and Performing Arts, Sharonville Elementary, Valerie Elementary, Whittier Junior High.
    - Oklahoma, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1382)
      Including: Wiley Post Elementary.
    - Oregon, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1383)
      Including: Carus School District #29.
    - Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1384-1390)
      Including: Brookline Elementary, Cumberland Valley High, Stephen Girard School, Grandview Elementary, J. R. Masterman Laboratory and Demonstration, Octorara Area Elementary School-Primary Building, The Pittsburgh High School for the Creative and Performing Arts.
    - Rhode Island, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1391)
      Including: Woonsocket Senior High.
    - South Carolina, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1392-1394)
      Including: D. W. Daniel High, Leaphart Elementary, Riverside High.
    - Tennessee, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1395-1397)
      Including: Grahamwood Elementary, Idlewild Elementary, Overton High.
    - Texas, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1398-1402)
      Including: Aldine Contemporary Education Center, Bowie High, Chula Vista Academy of Fine Arts, C. D. Fulkes Middle, Plano Senior High.
    - Utah, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1403)
      Including: North Servier Middle.
    - Vermont, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1404-1405)
      Including: Camels Hump Middle, St. Johnsbury Academy.
    - Virgin Islands, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1406)
    - Virginia, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1407-1408, Box 67, Folder 1409)
      Including: Patrick Henry Elementary, Old Donation Center for the Gifted and Talented, South Lakes High.
    - Washington, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 1410-1415)
      Including: Jefferson Elementary, Lakeridge and Island Park Elementary Schools, Medina Elementary, Shorewood High, Summit K-12 School, Sunset Elementary.
    - West Virginia, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 1416)
      Including: Putnam County Schools-Eastbrook Elementary School.
    - Wisconsin, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 1417-1418)
      Including: Elm Creative Arts School, Madison West Senior High.
  - Miscellaneous Materials Relating to Applications
    - Miscellaneous Material-Misplaced or Lost-from School Applicants, no date (Box 67, Folder 1419)
      - Animations – 3 to 6 grades - #10, 2016:FA776:073 (Box 67, Folder 1419)
    - RBF Arts Awards '81 - Evaluations, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1420-1421)
    - Music Schools Already Reviewed, no date (Box 67, Folder 1422)
    - Reviewer Comments/Judgments: Elementary Schools - Numerical Order, no date (Box 67, Folder 1423-1425)
    - Reviewer Comments/Judgments: Junior High Schools - Numerical Order, no date (Box 67, Folder 1426)
    - Reviewer Comments/Judgments: High Schools - Numerical Order, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 1427-1431)
    - Reviewer Comments/Judgments, no date (Box 68, Folder 1432)
    - Applications from Various Schools, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 1433)
    - Applications from Various Schools, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 1434-1436)